<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Wyndham Dreamland Bali</string>

    <string-array name="data_nama">
        <item>One Bedroom Suite</item>
        <item>One Bedroom Suite Ocean View</item>
        <item>One Bedroom Suite with Whirlpool</item>
        <item>One Bedroom Pool Villa</item>
        <item>Two-Bedroom Duplex Pool Villa and Whirlpool</item>
        <item>Two Bedroom Pool Villa</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="data_deskripsi">
        <item>starting from IDR 2.000.000/night get a room with a king size mattress</item>
        <item>starting from IDR 2.500.000/night get a room with a king size mattress with a dreamland beach view</item>
        <item>starting from IDR 3.000.000/night get a room with a king size bed with a living room and a whirlpool</item>
        <item>starting from IDR 5.000.000/night get a villa with a king size bed and private pool which is perfect for you who are on honeymoon</item>
        <item>starting from IDR 5.200.000/night get a villa with a king size bed and private outdoor swimming pool</item>
        <item>starting from IDR 8.000.000/night get a five star villa with two bedrooms and a king size bed and private pool</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="data_gambar">
        <item>@drawable/room1</item>
        <item>@drawable/room2</item>
        <item>@drawable/room3</item>
        <item>@drawable/villa1</item>
        <item>@drawable/villa2</item>
        <item>@drawable/villa3</item>
    </array>

    <string-array name="data_text">
        <item>The Wyndham Dreamland One-Bedroom Suite offers 72 square-meter with a generous living room and separate bedroom complete with king-size bed and luxury linens.
            Each One Bedroom Suite’s ensuite has a separate shower and deep soaking bathtub.</item>
        <item>A luxurious home away from home, the Ocean View Suite at Wyndham Dreamland Bali features 72 square-meter with a spacious private balcony and spectacular ocean views.
            Enjoy the comforts of a stylish living room and separate bedroom complete with king-size bed and luxury linens.</item>
        <item>Incorporating a host of inclusions to make your stay that little bit more special our One Bedroom Suite with Whirlpool is sure to impress even the most discerning of travellers.
            Features 72 square-meter include a king-size bed with luxury linens and a large balcony, while the direct whirlpool access provides the ultimate space for relaxation.</item>
        <item>This luxurious One Bedroom Pool Villa is ideal for the honeymoon couple with a spacious 112 square-meter area, every feature carefully selected to make your stay special and memorable.
            Each Villa has its own a private pool set amidst tropical gardens.</item>
        <item>Set amidst tropical gardens, the Two-Bedroom Duplex Pool Villa and Whirlpool is a luxurious private hideaway. This spacious 159 square-meter area sanctuary has two separate bedrooms and a living area with easy access to your gorgeous private outdoor swimming pool.
            The stylishly appointed bathroom features a double vanity, a separate shower and a luxurious deep soaking bathtub.</item>
        <item>The Two-Bedroom Private Pool Villa offers five-star luxury. With a spacious 163 square-meter area every imaginable amenity and sumptuous seclusion, this heavenly haven features two stylishly appointed bedrooms.
            Each has its own ensuite with a separate shower and deep soaking bath.</item>
    </string-array>
    
    <string-array name="data_adventages">
        <item>Enjoy tropical views from your spacious balcony and easy access to Dreamland Beach.</item>
        <item>The ensuite features a separate shower and deep soaking bathtub.</item>
        <item>This generously appointed suite also has its own separate living room and dedicated workspace.</item>
        <item>The stylishly appointed bathroom features a double vanity, a separate shower and a luxurious deep soaking bathtub.</item>
        <item>Soothe away your cares in your own whirlpool and enjoy romantic sunset dinners on the sea view terrace.</item>
        <item>Villas guests enjoy the added space of a separate living room with easy access to the Villa’s own private swimming pool.</item>
    </string-array>

    <array name="data_facilities">
        <item>Other features include a work desk, walk-in wardrobe, 42-inch flat-screen TV and free Wi-Fi.</item>
        <item>Other conveniences include a work desk, walk-in wardrobe, 42-inch flat-screen TV and free Wi-Fi.</item>
        <item>Other features include a walk-in wardrobe, ensuite with separate shower and deep soaking bathtub, 42-inch flat-screen TV and free Wi-Fi.</item>
        <item>Other conveniences include a work desk, walk-in wardrobe, 42-inch flat-screen TV and free Wi-Fi.</item>
        <item>Other conveniences include a work desk, walk-in wardrobe, 42-inch flat-screen TV and free Wi-Fi.</item>
        <item>Other conveniences include a work desk, walk-in wardrobe, 42-inch flat-screen TV and free Wi-Fi.</item>
    </array>

    <array name="data_harga">
        <item>IDR 2.000.000/night</item>
        <item>IDR 2.500.000/night</item>
        <item>IDR 3.000.000/night</item>
        <item>IDR 5.000.000/night</item>
        <item>IDR 5.200.000/night</item>
        <item>IDR 8.000.000/night</item>

    </array>
</resources>
